# Mohat Shil

Senior Software Test Engineer - 5 YOE - WEB | | MOBILE

https://github.com/shilCode | https://mohat.vercel.app/

**ABOUT ME** 

As a Senior Software Test Engineer with 5 years of experience in web and mobile application testing, I possess extensive knowledge of agile methodologies, test automation frameworks, and various testing tools including WebDriver IO, Playwright, and Jenkins. My academic credentials include a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science with a major in Quality Engineering and a minor in Cloud Engineering. I am seeking an opportunity to apply my skills and experience in a dynamic work environment.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **EPAM Systems**, Poland — Senior Software Testing Engineer

MAY 2022 - PRESENT

Scrum team collaboration, Requirements gathering, Acceptance criteria, Test planning, Stakeholder sign-off, Functional testing, Non-functional testing, Test Automation Framework, Regulatory compliance, Bug detection, Error reporting, Defect tracking, Communication, Risk management & Test improvements are some of my key responsibilities.

## **Keywords Studios**, Poland — *QA Lead*

**JULY 2021 - APRIL 2022** 

Project management, Workflow integration, Leadership, Client expectations, Team management, Communication, Feedback, Performance evaluation, Risk management, Data analysis, Decision-making, Agile methodology, Deadline management, Self-motivation, Attention to detail & Bug tracking and management

### **Testronic Labs**, Poland — Associate Lead

OCTOBER 2018 - JUNE 2021

Security procedures, Policy adherence, Test design, Mentoring, Task completion, Best practices, Line management, Staff evaluation, Client communication, Staffing management, Progress tracking, Bug vetting, Translation (LQA), Reporting, Coverage checklists, Testing duties & Time monitoring

## **EDUCATION**

**Vistula University**, Poland — Bachelors, Computer Science

JANUARY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2021 Major: Quality Engineering Szlak 41, 5/A Krakow, 31-161 +48 576727596 2850542@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

Test Automation Framework

**Testing Fundamentals** 

Agile Fundamentals (SCRUM)

CI/CD Fundamentals

UI E2E Testing | API Testing

BDD/TDD Fundamentals

A11y Testing

POM/OOP model using - DRY/KISS

**Test Estimation** 

Performance Test Fundamentals

#### **TECH STACK**

WebDriver IO (JS/TS/Python)

Playwright (JS/TS/Python)

Cypress (JS/TS)

Jenkins | BASH | Postman

Docker | Kubernetes

Testrail | Jira | Bugzilla

JMeter | OWASP

#### **LANGUAGES**

English - C1+ Bangla - Native